{
    "baseline" : { "question" : "Considering all parts of your life, how happy would you say you are?"},
    "generalqs_r1" : [
        { 
            "question" : "Do you find yourself thinking about death?",
            "scores" : {
                "social" : -0.1,
                "self" : 0,
                "meaning" : -0.2,
                "perspective" : -0.2
            }
        },
        {
            "question" : "Are you losing any sleep due to life stresses?",
            "scores" : {
                "social" : -0.1,
                "self" : -0.2,
                "meaning" : 0,
                "perspective" : -0.3
            }
        },
        {
            "question" : "Do you feel capable to make important decisions in your life?", 
            "scores" : {
                "social" : 0.1,
                "self" : 0.3,
                "meaning" : 0.1,
                "perspective" : 0.1
            }
        },
        {
            "question" : "Do you feel like you're constantly under strain?",
            "scores" : {
                "social" : -0.1,
                "self" : -0.3,
                "meaning" : 0,
                "perspective" : -0.2
            }
        },
        {
            "question" : "Are you able to enjoy your normal day-to-day activities?",
            "scores" : {
                "social" : 0.2,
                "self" : 0,
                "meaning" : 0.3,
                "perspective" : 0.1
            }
        },  
        {
            "question" : "Are you able clear your mind and concentrate?",
            "scores" : {
                "social" : 0.1,
                "self" : 0.4,
                "meaning" : 0.1,
                "perspective" : 0.2
            }
        }, 
        {
            "question" : "Do you feel good about your relationships with others?",
            "scores" : {
                "social" : 0.5,
                "self" : 0.3,
                "meaning" : -0.2,
                "perspective" : 0
            }
        },
        {
            "question" : "Do you feel you have a sense of purpose in the world?",
            "scores" : {
                "social" : 0.2,
                "self" : 0,
                "meaning" : 0.4,
                "perspective" : 0.1
            }
        },
        {
            "question" : "Do you feel your current behaviors aline with your values?",
            "scores" : {
                "social" : 0.1,
                "self" : 0,
                "meaning" : 0.2,
                "perspective" : -0.1
            }
        }
    ],

    "responses_r1" : [
        { "response" : "Not at All", "score": -2 },
        { "response" : "Less than usual", "score": -1 },
        { "response" : "No more than usual", "score": 0 },
        { "response" : "More than usual", "score": 1 },
        { "response" : "Most Definitely", "score": 2 }
    ],

    "socialqs_r2" : {
        "open_response" : ["Q1", "Q2", "Q3"],
        "word_association" : {
            "prompts" : ["P1", "P2", "P3"],
            "banks" : []
        },
        "conditioning" : {
            "actions" : ["A1", "A2", "A3"],
            "frequency" : []
        }
    },


    "selfqs_r2" : {
        "open_response" : ["Q1", "Q2", "Q3"],
        "word_association" : {
            "prompts" : ["P1", "P2", "P3"],
            "banks" : []
        },
        "conditioning" : {
            "actions" : ["A1", "A2", "A3"],
            "frequency" : []
        }
    },

    "meaningqs_r2" : {
        "open_response" : ["Q1", "Q2", "Q3"],
        "word_association" : {
            "prompts" : ["P1", "P2", "P3"],
            "banks" : []
        },
        "conditioning" : {
            "actions" : ["A1", "A2", "A3"],
            "frequency" : []
        }
    },

    "perspectiveqs_r2" : {
        "open_response" : ["Q1", "Q2", "Q3"],
        "word_association" : {
            "prompts" : ["P1", "P2", "P3"],
            "banks" : []
        },
        "conditioning" : {
            "actions" : ["A1", "A2", "A3"],
            "frequency" : []
        }
    }
}